Good afternoon
Добрый день
Hello from Ukraine, the city of
Здравствуйте из Украины город
Khmelnitsky, where are you from Russia,
Хмельницкий Вы откуда из России
Rostov-on-Don
ростов-на-дону
[music]
[музыка]
How do you feel about you, you are not in Ukraine
Как вы относитесь к вы не в Украине
normally, keep it normal.
нормально нормально держите получается
Of course
Конечно
, look how you feel about partially
вот смотрите как вы относитесь частично
mobilization in Russia.
мобилизации в России
than
сам бы пошел Если призвать Так а в чем
another military registration and enlistment office is closed or that you are
другого военкомат закрыт или что вас не
not allowed to study and that Well, it doesn’t
пускают не учеба и что Ну так не
look like he would have gone Well, they would have
выглядит сам бы пошел Ну призвали бы
gone, look, come in, call me
пошел смотрите заходите призывайте меня
all And you are calling for what is the problem as long as
все И вас призывает в чем проблема пока
my country has strength,
силы есть моей страны
look there have already utilized so many of
смотрите там уже столько
your orcs so recruit new ones
утилизировали ваших орков так новых
I’m mobilizing 300 thousand now, well,
набирать 300 тысяч мобилизирую сейчас ну
as it is Why are the
как это есть Почему
occupiers a person who has to be
оккупанты человек который приходится
Why
Почему
guys Well, she’s in the Donbass what did you do there
ребят Ну она Донбассе чего вы делали там
8 fought against Russian terrorists Yes,
8 боролись с российскими террористами Да
who came there there was no [ __ ] yes A
которые пришли там не было [__] да А
girking who was on the 14th How
гиркинг кто такой был 14 числа С чего
did it all start in general
началась все вообще
Listen and Bandera  Come on then such a
Слушай а Бандера Давай тогда такой
Bandera in the Donbass,
Бандера на донбасселю
let's talk about the Donbass, don't invite us on the
давай про Донбасс ты не пригости мы на
topic, are you already if for the Donba  ss hinted at 2
тему ты уже если за Донбасс заикнулся 2
Donbass
Донбасс
When the war in the Donbass began, say
Когда началась война на Донбассе скажи
here 4 on April 12, 2014, when
вот 4 12 апреля 2014 года когда
Russian militants led
российские боевики до под
by Girkin the FSB officer entered
предводительством гиркина фсбшника зашли
and captured the Peaceful City of Slavyansk before
и захватили Мирный город Славянск до
that, at least some military operations in the
этого хоть какие-то боевые действия на
Donbass were
Донбассе были
all
все
these things, all these star-weavers, that's when with
вещи эти все звездоплеты вот когда с
they start with the facts right away. In short,
ними начинаешь по фактам сразу Короче у
they have something shorter
них что-то короче
[music] the
[музыка]
face
лицо
on the air
в прямом эфире
must be clearly based on the facts and they are a minute
надо четко по фактам и они минута я не
away.  they
Никто из всех этих там
support the operation there, maybe
поддерживают операцию рассказать бомбили
no one was bombing, and people
не был никто и люди
even support nothing until the
даже поддерживают ничего пока не пришли
Russians came, these terrorists didn’t start to
российские вот эти террористы не начали
seize the cities of dude Wagner Yes, he
захватывать города чувака Вагнер Да
pulled himself up Yes, there’s
подтянулся ещё это ж Да возле уже
already even an interval near Prigozhin, so
Пригожин уже даже интервал поэтому
everything was fine there were ordinary rallies
всё было нормально были обычные митинги
and in Ukraine always  we had free people,
и в Украине всегда были у нас люди
they have the right to go to
свободные они имеют право выходить на
rallies, so someone is there with such ideas,
митинги так кто-то там с такими идеями
someone  there were no armed clashes with such people
кто-то с такими никаких вооруженных
,
столкновений не было
but Russian terrorists came and began to
но пришли российские террористы начали
seize cities, kill residents of
захватывать города убивать жителей
Donbass, until the first victims, it was precisely the
Донбасса до первые жертва как раз именно
inhabitants of Donbass that the deputies of the city
жители Донбасса депутаты городского
council of Gorlovsky with passwords threw his stomach
совета горловского с паролей ему живот
into the river, everything is
Кинули в речку все есть официально
official data, you can see,
официальные данные можно посмотреть
you can say yes there,
можно сказать да туда
but rashists  there is no information what
а рашистов нет никакой информации что
it is somehow Ukraine Bombila Bombila
это такое как-то Украина Бомбила Бомбила
Donbass but no one can And when the wife
Донбасс но никто не может А когда жена
then Bombila they all bring already when there
тогда Бомбила они все приводят уже когда
were full-fledged hostilities until When
шли полноценные боевые действия до Когда
Russia these all Russian militants
Россия эти все российские боевики
invaded there they captured cities,
вторгались там захватывали города
shelled
обстреливали
Ukrainian and military units and
украинские и воинские части и мирняк
Ukrainian civilians  too So they are already serving
украинский тоже Так они уже подают вот
these military operations like Ukraine Bombed
эти боевые действия как Украина Бомбила
Donbass is sitting There, it
Донбасс сидит Там просто
's just that we have it calmly, then everything is shorter in the
вот у нас спокойно то все короче на
Donbass, let's go
Донбассе давайте мы
OK Subscribe
Окей Подписывайтесь